

Albane MAGNIN

Contact

71570 La Chapelle de Guinchay



B license | 30 years old

06 21 98 41 45

magninalb@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/albane-

https://github.com/Albane-

MAGNIN

https://albane-

magnin.github.io/Portfolio/

Language

French: native

English: CLES B2

Expertise

ReactJS **Javascript** SCSS HTML5

CSS

IT tools

Linux GitHub Agile method Azur DevOps

Projects

Available on my GitHub account and my portfolio.

About me

After more than two years of experience as a QA in the payroll department, I was fascinated by the job of an IT developer.

September 2022, I started training to become a Web and Mobile Web Developer and professional obtained my qualification in June 2023.

transition is a natural based progression experience, analytical skills, passion for technology and willingness to learn.

Web developer

Experience

• February 2023 - March 2023

O'Clock School

Front-end developer - ReactJS

Team of 4 developers : 3 front & 1 back.

Develop a comprehensive travel application for outdoor enthusiasts in France, featuring curated lists of the best camping spots and must-visit destinations in the surrounding areas.

March 2019 - October 2021

Full | Software editor

December 2019 - October 2021

Payroll quality referent | Team of 3 QA

In charge of:

- Size workload for the team
- Manage deadlines
- Train and support payroll quality employees
- Same missions as those for the position of payroll quality controller

March 2019 - December 2019

Payroll quality controller

In collaboration with lawyers, modellers and developers teams:

- Drafting, run, and validate tests to deploy in clients DB
- Drafting clients and internals documentations
- July 2018 January 2019

Toupargel Groupe | Distribution group specialized in home grocery delivery

Payroll expert - Sage i7 & SAP

In charge of:

- · Software updates, social monitoring
- Manage payroll periods
- · Bank transfers (wages, salary installments), statement of charges, social and accounting reporting
- Producing internal documents
- November 2014 March 2018

CONSULTYS | Pharmaceutical engineering consultancy

June 2017 - March 2018

Software migration manager and replacement of the payroll social manager - Sage X3

- Migration Ciel Paie to Sage X3
 - o Definition of needs, development of specifications, internal audit
 - Optimization of practices, establishment of internal procedures
 - Exchanges, meetings and training with the consulting firm
 - Start-up with respect to deadlines and provisional planning
- · Payroll, personnel administration, social monitoring (200 employees); management 1 employee

November 2014 - June 2017

Payroll and personnel administration administrator

French and Belgian payrolls

Assignements: payroll, absenteeism, personnel administration, training

Formation

- September 2022 March 2023 O'Clock School | Professional Certificate RNCP Level 5 Web & mobile web developer, specializing in ReactJS
 - 3 months learning: Javascript, PHP, Laravel, SQL, design pattern MVC, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap
 - 1 month: specialization in ReactJS
 - 1 month: development of the Day & Night application
- September 2013 September 2014 Université Claude Bernard Lyon 1 | Bachelor's degree Organizational management, major human relations
- September 2011 September 2013 Université Lumière Lyon 2 | University diploma Business and administration management, major human relations